System Dynamic Society; Records ua435
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
System Dynamic Society Records
1978-2016
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
System Dynamics Society
ua435
5.85 cubic ft.
Adminsrative records of the System Dynamic Society, a professional organization of academics devoted to furthering research into system dynamics and systems thinking. The Society holds an annual international conference, and the administration of the group was based at UAlbany until 2018.
Content Description
Contains administrative records for running the professional organization and annual conference for System Dynamics. Includes conference promotional materials, meeting records, proceedings and photographs from conferences, membership directories, budget documentation, annual reports, correspondence with publishers, newsletters, and games designed by the Society to teach System Dynamics. Also includes A/V materials, mostly from 2000s-2010s and born digital records on external media which is likely copies of material in the web archives and that will be transferred over network shares.
Biographical / Historical
The System Dynamics Society is an international, nonprofit organization devoted to encouraging the development and use of System Dynamics and systems thinking around the world. The Society provides a forum in which researchers, educators, students, consultants and practitioners in the academic, corporate and public sectors interact to keep abreast of current developments, build on each other's work and introduce newcomers to the field. The Society manages the annual International Conference of the System Dynamics Society and publishes the System Dynamics Review. Originally founded at MIT, the Society was later administered at UAlbany until 2018 where they recieved some state funded assistance for their administration, as well as funding from members and sponsoring organizations. After 2018 the Society was supported by an outside vendor in Albany.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted unless otherwide denoted.
Arrangement
The collections was arranged by Society staff members during their office closing.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by the System Dynamics Society in October 2018.
Dynamics
- Conferences, 1976-2018
  Scope and Contents
  Contains the website for the annual conference along with the published conference proceedings.
  Biographical / Historical
  The System Dynamic Society holds an annual international conference to allow local chapters and interest group to meet, introduce newcomers to the field, keep practitioners aware of current developments, and provide networking opportunities. The event is held alternately in North America and Europe, with occasional appearances in Asia and the Pacific Rim.
  - Albuquerque, NM, USA, 2019 July 21-25
  - Reykjavík, Iceland, 2018 August 6-2018 August 10
    - Conference Website, 2018 August 6-2018 August 10
    - Conference Booklet & Sponsors, 2018 August 6-2018 August 10
    - Conference Record, 2018 August 6-2018 August 10
    - Papers, 2018 August 6-2018 August 10
    - Conference Photos, 2018 August 6-2018 August 10
  - Cambridge, MA, USA, 2017 July 16-2017 July 20
    - Conference Website, 2017 July 16-2017 July 20
    - Sessions by Thread, 2017 July 16-2017 July 20
    - Conference Booklet, 2017 July 16-2017 July 20
    - Papers, 2017 July 16-2017 July 20
    - Chapter and SIG E-posters, 2017 July 16-2017 July 20
    - Conference Photos, 2017 July 16-2017 July 20
    - Sponsors, 2017 July 16-2017 July 20
  - Singapore, 2nd Asia-Pacific Region System Dynamics Conference, 2017 February 19-22
  - Delft, Netherlands, 2016 July 17-2016 July 21
    - Conference Website, 2016 July 17-2016 July 21
    - Sessions by Thread, 2016 July 17-2016 July 21
    - Conference Booklet, 2016 July 17-2016 July 21
    - Papers, 2016 July 17-2016 July 21
    - Chapter and SIG E-posters, 2016 July 17-2016 July 21
    - Conference Photos, 2016 July 17-2016 July 21
    - Sponsors, 2016 July 17-2016 July 21
  - Cambridge, MA, USA, 2015 July 19-2015 July 23
    - Conference Website, 2015 July 19-2015 July 23
    - Sessions by Thread, 2015 July 19-2015 July 23
    - Conference Booklet, 2015 July 19-2015 July 23
    - Papers, 2015 July 19-2015 July 23
    - Chapter and SIG E-posters, 2015 July 19-2015 July 23
    - Sponsors, 2015 July 19-2015 July 23
    - Sponsor Notes, 2015 July 19-2015 July 23
  - Delft, Netherlands, 2014 July 20-2014 July 24
    - Conference Website, 2014 July 20-2014 July 24
    - Sessions by Thread, 2014 July 20-2014 July 24
    - Abstract Proceedings, 2014 July 20-2014 July 24
    - Papers, 2014 July 20-2014 July 24
    - Chapter and SIG E-posters, 2014 July 20-2014 July 24
    - Sponsors, 2014 July 20-2014 July 24
    - Sponsor Notes, 2014 July 20-2014 July 24
  - Tokyo, Japan, Asia-Pacific System Dynamics Conference, 2014 February 22-24
  - Cambridge, MA, USA, 2013 July 21-2013 July 25
    - Conference Website, 2013 July 21-2013 July 25
    - Sessions by Thread, 2013 July 21-2013 July 25
    - Abstract Proceedings, 2013 July 21-2013 July 25
    - Papers, 2013 July 21-2013 July 25
    - Chapter and SIG E-posters, 2013 July 21-2013 July 25
    - Sponsors, 2013 July 21-2013 July 25
    - Sponsor Notes, 2013 July 21-2013 July 25
  - St. Gallen, Switzerland, 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
    - Conference Website, 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
    - Sessions by Thread, 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
    - Abstract Proceedings, 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
    - Papers, 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Aamir, Munaf with Vanessa Vargas, "Model of Drivers of Fear-Induced Consumer Avoidance Behaviors Post-Incident", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Alessi, Stephen with Birgit Kopainsky and Erling Moxnes, "Teaching Resource Management with Web-Based Models and Multi-Player Games", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Alexiev, Victor, "Measuring Group Model Building Intervention Impact Through Preference Elicitation", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Almaguer Prado, Pedro Dagoberto with Ramiro Luis Almaguer Navarro, Ruth Raquel Almaguer Navarro, Pedro Dagoberto Almaguer Navarro and Beatriz Eugenia Navarro Vazquez, "POLLEN learning lab to improve the public education system and PISA", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Altamirano, Mónica with Karen Meijer, Lija van Vliet and Arjen Ros, "An exploration of the added value of Systems Analysis and System Dynamics for assessing the importance of innovative concepts", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Arenas, Fernando, "Stocks of Knowledge and Organizational Performance: A Dynamic Relationship", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Armenia, Stefano with Andrea Centra, Vittorio Cesarotti, Angelo De Angelis and Clarissa Retrosi, "Military Workforce Dynamics and Planning in the Italian AirForce", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Atzori, Alberto Stanislao with David Ford, Luis Tedeschi and Antonello Cannas, "Policy Modeling for Greenhouses Gas Emissions on Dairy Cattle Sector: the Importance of the Milk Production Improvement", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Auping, Willem with Erik Pruyt and Jan Kwakkel, "Analysing the Uncertain Future of Copper with Three Exploratory System Dynamics Models", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Baitello, André with Marcelo Ramos Martins, "Organizational learning effects in productivity: a dynamic hypothesis proposal for shipyard learning", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Balaporia, Zahir with Mike Zeimer, "Games for Learning in Freight Transportation Systems", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Barnabe, Federico with Cristiano Busco, Maurizio Lambri and Gianfranco Zatta, "Matching Role Playing, Balanced Scorecards and System Dynamics modelling in management training: the "Strategic Micro-Factory"", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Bean, Michael, "Developing Business Simulation Games for a Mainstream Audience", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Beck, Abby with Krystyna Stave, "Understanding Urban Quality of Life and Sustainability: Model Development and Validation", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Bier, Asmeret, "Organizational Participation in Cooperative Cyber Security", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Bishwas, Sumant with Sushil Sushil, "Knowledge Management and Related Emerging Issues in Organizations: A Systems Thinking using Feedback Loop Analysis", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Bisilkas, Marios with Aurora Garcia-Gallego and Ivan Barreda Tarrazona, "Services as an Alternative Path to Sustainability", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Bisilkas, Marios with Ivan Barreda Tarrazona and Aurora Garcia-Gallego, "A Model of the Sustainability Requirements Dynamics for New Product Development", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Blaskovich, Frank, "Oil Policy Regret Analysis With System Dynamics Models", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Browne, Chris with Haley Jones and Paul Compston, "Is it Really Greener in the Cloud? An Investigation of Energy Trends in Cloud Computing (Best Poster Award Winner)", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Buendia, Fernando, "Expansion Economies: The Growth of the Firm through its Globalization", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Buendia, Fernando, "The Reward System in Art Markets: a System Dynamics approach", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Campos-Lopez, Enrique with Alena Urdiales-Kalinchuk, Arturo Inda-Cunningham, Helue De la Barrera-Gomez and Avelino Hernandez-Corichi, "Spore: an Action-Learning Support System for Incubating Regional Cooperative Innovation Networks", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Carena, Augusto, "Midday in Athens. A Socratic Dialogue about Systems", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Chaim, Ricardo, "ERM quantitative risk analysis methods and techniques applied to a small commercial bank", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Chaudhuri, Saikat with Abhijit Mandal, "High-Value Outsourcing: Impact of Team Structure and Capabilities on Complex and Uncertain Off-shoring Projects", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Choi, Jeong Hwan with Seongpil Ko and Jeong Dong Lee, "Research on make or buy decision making strategy using System Dynamics: Focused on Korea's military improvement project", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Chuang, Howard Hao-Chun with Rogelio Oliva and Olga Perdikaki, "Retail Sales Generation: A Methodological Comparison of Econometric Estimation and Calibration", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Corcoran, Stan with Alan Graham, William Arthur and David Peterson, "A Competitor's Strategy Unclothed: How Indirect Measurement Justified Not Fighting an Insurance Price War", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Das, Dillip, "Planning and Management of Regional Infrastructure for Tourism Development in Orissa State, India", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - de Gooyert, Vincent with Christian Erik Kampmann, "Revisiting the Roberts-Levin Patient Dropout Model (Lupina Award Winner)", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - de Groen, André with Erik Pruyt and Harry Boumeester, "Dutch social housing sector reforms: Exploring the effects on low income households", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - De Marco, Alberto with Anna Cagliano and Carlo Rafele, "Forecasting the Diffusion of a Mobile Service for Freight Distribution", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Dianati, Kaveh with Roland Maximilian Happach, "The Rise and Fall of the U.S. Homicide Rate towards the End of the 20th Century - A System Dynamics Approach", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Doganca, Zerrin with Ali Saysel, "An Interview Protocol for Assessing Students' Understanding of Dynamically Complex Environmental Problems", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Domenge Munoz, Rogerio, "Power Generation Capacity Planning Under Ecological, Security and Economic Criteria: The Mexican Case", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Duggan, Jim, "An Extended SIR Model to Explore the Impact of Syndromic Data Sources on Social Distancing Policy", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Eberlein, Robert with James Thompson, "Chronological Aging in Continuous Time", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Eker, Sibel with Cornelia van Daalen, "Uncertainties in the Development of Unconventional Gas in the Netherlands", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - El Halabi, Ezzat with Matthew Doolan and Michael Cardew-Hall, "Extracting Variables and Causal Links from Interview Data", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Elias, Arun with Saji Mathew, "Offshore IT outsourcing between India and New Zealand: A Qualitative System Dynamics Model", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Elmasry, Shady with Mohamed Shalaby and Mohamed Saleh, "A System dynamics simulation model for scalable-capacity manufacturing systems", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Enos, James, "Dynamics of Reconstruction Projects", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Enos, James, "Learning with Loops: Applying Feedback to Teaching System Dynamics to Undergraduates", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Eren, Aysen, "A System Dynamics Model of a Local Economy with Bi-Currency System", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Escalante, Nicolas, "Model Conceptualization for Sustainable Waste and Resource Management Policy Design in Low and Middle-Income Countries", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Eskinasi, Martijn, "Collected System Dynamics works on recent real estate dynamics", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Eslamifar, Gholamreza with Amir MohammadShirazi and Ali Mashayekhi, "A System Dynamics model to achieve sustainable production of oil in Iran", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Farr, Warren, "Using System Dynamics to Create Durable Business Strategy- US Air Conditioning Industry Case Study", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Featherston, Charles with Matthew Doolan, "A Critical Review of the Criticisms of System Dynamics", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Fischer, Helen with Christina Degen, "Stock-flow failure can be explained by the task design", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Ford, Andrew with Thuy Nguyen and Allyson Beall, "Modeling Support for National Park Planning: Initial Results from a Case Study of Glacier National Park", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Gaynor, Alan, "Different Kids—How Typical Schools Are Built to Fail and Need to Change: A Structural Analysis", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Georgantzas, Nicholas, "Time out politics: transforming time into space", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Golnam, Arash with Ron Sanchez, Gorica Tapandjieva and Alain Wegmann, "Choosing the Right Tool for the Job: A Framework to Compare the Effectiveness of Problem Structuring Methods in System Dynamics", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Gomez Diaz, Mauricio with Navid Ghaffarzadegan and Richard Larson, "Unintended Effects of Changes in NIH Appropriations: Challenges for Biomedical Research Workforce Development (Barry Richmond Award Winner)", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Gramlich, Dieter with Mikhail Oet, "Systemic Financial Feedbacks - Conceptual Framework and Modeling Implications", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Grassmann, Winfried with Jin Zhang, Roland Dyck and Nathaniel Osgood, "A System Simulation Model for Type 2 Diabetes in the Saskatoon Health Region", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Groessler, Andreas with Jürgen Strohhecker, "Tangible Stock/Flow Experiments -- Addressing Issues of Naturalistic Decision Making", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Haag, Hans-Christian with Meike Tilebein, "Integrating System Dynamics in a Strategic Foresight Process for Firms in Production Networks", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Hackett, Stian, "Fuel taxes as an energy saving policy – potential misperceptions of dynamic effects", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Hadjis, Andreas with George Papageorgiou, "Planning via System Dynamics Models; Strategy Dynamics of Market Evolution", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Hamarat, Caner with Erik Pruyt and Jan Kwakkel, "Adaptive Policymaking under Deep Uncertainty: Optimal Preparedness for the next pandemic", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Hamza, Kanar with Karl Rich and David Wheat, "The role of System Dynamics approaches in aquatic disease management: an application to sea lice control in Norway", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Handel, Oliver with Aziiz Sutrisno, "Dynamic Aging Population in Germany: A case study about demographic change", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Happach, Roland Maximilian with Guido Veldhuis, Jac Vennix and Etiënne Rouwette, "Group Model Validation", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Hayward, John, "Model Behavior and the Strengths of Causal Loops: Mathematical Insights and a Practical Method", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Heslop, Benjamin, "Modelling Collaboration to optimise Innovation", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Heyder, Monika with Alessandra Goetz, Susanne Schmidt, Maria Sipowicz, Pablo Viejo Garcia and Simon Aulagnier, "Climate Change Actions in the Urban Context: A Tool for Decision Makers", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Hidayatno, Akhmad with Armand Moeis, Nuzul Achjar and Aziiz Sutrisno, "Communicating Complexity in Indonesia's Electricity Economics and Market Development Using System Dynamics Based Game", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Hirsch, Gary with Khalid Saeed, Karl McCleary and Kevin Myer, "Deceased Donor Potential for Organ Transplantation: A System Dynamics Framework", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Hirsch, Gary with Jack Homer, Bobby Milstein, John Sterman, Christina Ingersol, Leigh Scherrer, Laura Landy and Elliott Fisher, "ReThink Health Dynamics: Understanding and Influencing Local Health System Change", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Ho, Yu-Feng with Hsiao-Lin Wang and Cheng-Chih Liu, "System Dynamics and Genetic Artificial Neural Network Models for the Monitoring and Early Warning of Urban Housing Market", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Holmberg, Stig with Daniel Dubois, "SDA: System Dynamics Simulation of Inter Regional Risk Management Using a Multi-Layered Model with Delays and Anticipation", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Hovmand, Peter with Alissa Nelson and Kenneth Carson, "Understanding Social Determinants from the Ground Up", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Hovmand, Peter with Matthew Kreuter and James Dearing, "Designing Public Health Dissemination and Delivery Systems", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Ip, Edward with Mark Wolfson, Douglas Easterling, Erin Sutfin, Kimberly Wagoner, Jill Blocker, Kathleen Egan, Hazhir Rahmandad and Shyu-Huei Chen, "Agent-based modeling of College Drinking Behavior and mapping of feedback mechanism of alcohol reduction", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Joffe, Michael, "Competition Between Firms – System Dynamics and Other Approaches", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - John, Klaus, "Linking Economic Modeling and System Dynamics: A Basic Model for Monetary Policy and Macroprudential Regulation", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Kaiser, Jasmin with Peter Buxmann, "Toward a Dynamic View on Client Dependence in IS Outsourcing Relationships: A Qualitative System Dynamics Approach", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Kapmeier, Florian with Jörg Gerigk, ""Small changes can cause big problems over time": Insights from a Systems Thinking Intervention on Ecosystems with 4th graders", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Keijser, Bas with Jan Kwakkel and Erik Pruyt, "How to Explore and Manage the Future? Formal Model Analysis for Complex Issues under Deep Uncertainty", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Kendall, Merrill, "The Wizard of Oz & System Dynamics' Application to System Test", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Khosla, Karan, ""Strategy Dynamics of a Social Enterprise in India" – Impacts of System Dynamics on conventional strategy formulation", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Kieckhafer, Karsten with Katharina Wachter, Joachim Axmann and Thomas Spengler, "Model-based Decision Support for Future OEM Power-train Portfolios: Academic Solutions for Practical Requirements", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Kim, Amy with Vahid Faghihi, Amir R. Hessami and David Ford, "Designing Perpetual Sustainability Improvement Programs for Built Infrastructures", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Kim, Dong-Hwan with Khalid Saeed, "Institutional political dynamics: political cycles between the liberal and the conservative", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Koca, Deniz with Harald Sverdrup, "Using Casual Loop Diagrams & Systems Analysis to Explore Alternative Climate Change Adaptation Strategies in Seyhan River Basin", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Kopainsky, Birgit with Maria Saldarriaga, "Assessing understanding and learning about dynamic systems", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Kovari, András with Erik Pruyt, "Prostitution and Human Trafficking: A model-based exploration and policy analysis (Dana Meadows Award Winner)", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Kovriga, Svetlana with Nina Abramova, "Criterial Approach to Verification at Cognitive Mapping of Ill-Structured Situation Dynamics", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Krail, Michael with Wolfgang Schade, "Reducing the Climate Impact of Transport – Technologies and Policies for Road Transport", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Kuehn, André with Simon Gloeser, "System-Based Feedback Analysis of E-Mobility Diffusion in China", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Kumar, Ashwani with Kwong Meng Teo and Amedeo Odoni, "A Systems Perspective of Cycling and Bike-sharing Systems in Urban Mobility", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Kunc, Martin, "Modeling Start-ups using System Dynamics: Towards a generic model", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Kunc, Martin, "System Dynamics and Innovation: A complex problem with multiple levels of analysis", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Kwakkel, Jan with Jos Timmermans, "Exploratory System Dynamics: a directed search for limits to global water use", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Kwakkel, Jan with Jill Slinger, "A System Dynamics Model-Based Exploratory Analysis of Salt Water Intrusion in Coastal Aquifers", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Lafond, Daniel with Ashley Beattie, Michel DuCharme and Sébastien Tremblay, "Collaborative Decision Making in a Simulated Stability Operations Exercise: A Prototype Decision Support Tool", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Lee, Carmen with James Thompson and Robert Eberlein, "The cause of growing foreign-trained nurse concentration and its impact", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Leopold, Armin with Bo Hu, Klaus Arto and Irina Dolgopolova, "Germany's Electricity Industry in 2025: Evaluation of Portfolio Concepts", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Lerch, Christian with Thomas Schmall and Matthias Gotsch, "Linking Innovation and Service Productivity - An analysis of interactive effects in knowledge-intensive business services", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Levin, Ilya with Tzur Levin, "Hybrid Models in Developing System Thinking", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Li, Anson with Kambiz Maani, "A Supply Chain Paradox", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Logtens, Thomas with Erik Pruyt and Govert Gijsbers, "Societal Aging in the Netherlands: Exploratory System Dynamics Modeling and Analysis (Lupina Award Winner)", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Lopez, Luis with Roy Zuniga, "The Dynamics of a Judicial Service Supply Chain: A case study", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Lowry, Thomas with Sean McKenna, Teklu Hadgu and Elena Kalinina, "Using System Dynamics for Uncertainty Analysis and Integrated Risk Assessment in Geothermal Energy Development", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - Mavrommati, Georgia with Kostas Bithas and Panayiotis Panayiotidis, "A System Dynamics Bioeconomic Model for Ecologically Sustainable Economic Development in Coastal Ecosystems", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26
      - McDowall, Richard, "How Do "Short Sharp Shock" Punishments Affect the Prison Population? A System Dynamics Study of the London Riot Sentences", 2012 July 22-2012 July 26